Chapter 4: A Fierce Battle

The day finally came for Lucius and Reiss to execute their plan to kidnap Celia, just two days after Lucius made his arrangements to get the jump on his partner. However...

In the skies several kilometers east of Rodania, two shadows were chasing each other through the air at a tremendous speed. The shadow in front was Reiss, and the one giving chase was Aishia.

You’ve done it now, Lucius. I never imagined a betrayal at the last moment like that...

Reiss flew at his maximum speed to flee from Aishia while recalling the events from several moments ago with an annoyed grimace. Reiss and Lucius had visited the central office of the Restoration together.

“It seems like Princess Christina and Princess Flora are returning by airship, so everyone’s in a rush. I didn’t think everyone in the central office would be out, though...” Reiss said, gazing out the window.

“Maybe something’s happened. So what are we gonna do? Shouldn’t Celia’s lecture be over soon?” Lucius asked with a faint smile.

If everything was occurring as he planned, Arein and the others would have sent Christina and Flora to the Paladia Forest already. Based on the look of things, it had gone well, making him chuckle to himself on the inside.

“She normally returns to her estate from the front entrance, but with this many people out and about, we won’t be able to attack her within the premises. Oh dear...” Reiss looked towards the door as though he noticed something.

“What is it?”

“It’s extremely faint, but I can detect a spirit’s presence approaching. As expected, it must be the contract spirit of the Black Knight. It seems like it’s in spirit form right now, but even in spirit form it’s giving off a faint presence. How terrifying,” Reiss said with a light shrug.

“...Isn’t it going to notice your presence too?” Lucius checked.

“Veiling my presence is my forte, but even I’d be noticed at close range. If the spirit’s got sharp senses for detection, it may even notice that we’ve stopped by this room.”

“I see. So what now? Do we attack it in this room? Or wait for it to go outside?” Lucius asked in a rather calm tone.

“If it passes by the room then we’ll go after it, but if it enters this room then we’ll do it here. If it enters the room, you should handle it. The contract spirit should show itself immediately, so while you’re fighting the spirit, I will apprehend Celia Claire,” Reiss said somewhat rapidly, as though he was pressed for time.

“I see.”

“It’ll be here soon, so you should move next to the door.”

“Right.” Lucius approached the door as instructed. Shortly afterwards, someone knocked on it.

“They’re here... What are you doing?” Reiss whispered. His attention had been drawn to the door, but he frowned in suspicion when he saw Lucius take two magic crystals out of his breast pocket.

“I’ll show you a little mercy and erase my tracks when I go.”

“What are you—” Reiss’s confusion intensified.

Lucius immediately activated the magic crystal. “Transilio.” At the same time, he dropped the other magic crystal in his hand onto the ground.

“What?!” Reiss’s eyes widened in surprise. That was the last he saw of Lucius before he disappeared. The space distorted and Lucius vanished in an instant.

Meanwhile, the barrier spell in the magic crystal Lucius had dropped absorbed all the magic essence emitted by the space sorcery. A circle of light roughly one meter in radius appeared, completely shutting off the torrent of ode and mana from leaking outside. Even its creator, Reiss, wouldn’t have noticed the sorcery being activated if he hadn’t seen it with his bare eyes—the exceptional quality had backfired on him.

“Excuse me...”

Immediately after that, Celia entered the room.

◇　◇　◇

Several minutes later, in the skies above the east Rodanian outskirts...

Good grief. After all I did to emphasize how capturing Celia Claire would be the best possible move for him. Do you detest my interference that much, Lucius?

Reiss sighed, wondering when the last time he felt so panicked was. When he looked over his shoulder, he could see Aishia hot on his tail.

Having entrusted Celia to Sara and the others, Aishia was rid of her burden and able to increase her speed. Reiss also accelerated, but the distance between them was slowly growing shorter.

She’s definitely getting closer. We’ll soon be out of the forest and out in the open wasteland with nowhere to hide. It’ll only be a matter of time before she catches up... I guess I have no other choice.

Fleeing would be a challenge at this rate. With that thought, Reiss resolved himself. The moment he flew out of the forest, he descended rapidly. He landed first on the level wasteland and waited for Aishia to come down as well.

“Had enough of running?” Aishia asked after descending several meters away.

“Yes. I could see you would catch up soon at the rate we were going.”

“Indeed,” Aishia replied shortly. She quietly assumed a battle-ready stance.

“If I promise never to sneak into Rodania ever again, would you let me go?” Reiss suddenly pleaded for his life.

“No.”

“Then how about a little chat? I’m quite interested in you.”

“I’m not interested in you,” Aishia replied flatly.

“Hmm. Spirits develop a stronger sense of self with the passing of time and increase in rank, becoming more similar in appearance and personality to humans, but your sense of self is awfully faint. You’ve reached the realms of a humanoid spirit, yet you’re more like a newborn one. Do you even know who you are?” Reiss stared at Aishia as though to ascertain her identity.

“You don’t seem like a human either... There’s something eerie about your aura. It’s inhuman. Similar to a spirit, but more repulsive than a monster.”

“Oh? Have you developed a little interest in me, then?”

“...” A slight discomfort appeared in Aishia’s expression for the first time. Reiss didn’t let that slip past him and grinned arrogantly.

“Hahaha, so you can express emotions after all.”

“I’d rather remain the way I am than express emotions like yours.”

“So you can make self-assertions too. By the way, it seems you have rather sharp senses, but I’m not a spirit,” Reiss boasted with an empty smile. There was no telling how much of his words were true or not. It was a cunning tone.

“I have no intention of chatting with you any further,” Aishia stated flatly, her magic essence swelling.

“What if the reason why I bought all this time was because my true aim was to grab Celia Claire?”

“Celia is with Sara and the others. I can return instantly at this distance too.” Aishia activated her spirit arts in a show of her confidence. Light bullets of magic essence appeared around her, locking their aim onto Reiss.

“How awfully calm of you. Well, that wasn’t my true aim anyway—really. That’s why I’d like you to let me go... Whoa!”

“Get over yourself.” Aishia fired the light projectiles with a stern expression, fed up with Reiss’s babbling. Contrary to his joking attitude, Reiss didn’t let down his guard at all, reacting at an incredible speed to leap to the side and avoid the attack.

However, Aishia had already fired other bullets with trajectories she could freely control, making them aim for Reiss from every angle.

“Goodness.” Reiss immediately sighed heavily and released an enormous amount of darkness from his entire body. The darkness completely swallowed Aishia’s light and promptly contracted in size.

“...” Aishia watched on with an extremely wary look. She was concerned about the darkness that had swelled up—it wouldn’t be wise to approach carelessly, she realized.

“To think I’d have to reveal my abilities for the mere purpose of fleeing...” Reiss said with a sigh. Then, the shadow at his feet expanded rapidly, staining the surrounding ground pitch black. The next moment, minotaurs with massive stone greatswords and several creatures resembling Winged Lizards—a flying subspecies of dragon—appeared. They were all jet black in color.

“...Monsters?” Minotaurs were naturally categorized as monsters, but Aishia sensed a monster-like aura from the winged creatures as well.

“I do not wish to be killed, so I’ll be resisting you with everything I have. Well, I’ll do what I can in this situation. It’s a good chance for me to play with my collection as well.” At the same time Reiss finished speaking his words, the minotaurs and winged creatures moved to surround Aishia.

“MROOOR!” One minotaur took a giant leap, directly attacking Aishia. It moved above her head instantly, carrying the momentum of its fall behind the swing of its stone greatsword.

A thundering impact echoed. The surrounding ground cracked, and the minotaur was certain it had made contact. However, the stone greatsword hadn’t crushed Aishia’s body.

“Grah?!”

In an unexpected turn of events, an invisible wall surrounding Aishia had blocked the minotaur’s greatsword. The minotaur reacted in surprise and placed more weight and strength into pressing the sword forward, but the arm holding the sword merely trembled without moving an inch.

“Move,” Aishia muttered, placing her hand against the minotaur.

“Gwoh?!”

Aishia shot a powerful shock wave from the palm of her hand, blowing away the giant body of the minotaur. It flew through the air and crashed to the ground, skidding a dozen or so meters from where it landed.

“Gah... ah...” The minotaur had no strength left to stand and turned to ash on the ground, leaving behind a magic gem.

“Even an enhanced minotaur can’t lift a finger against you, I see. How about an attack from the skies, then?” Reiss said, and the winged creatures in the air opened their mouths. They spewed flaming hot breaths towards Aishia. The breath had enough heat to burn a human into ash, but Aishia easily evaded the fiery downpour with light footwork.

“Winged Lizards shouldn’t be able to breathe fire...” Once she evaded all the breaths and came to a stop, she looked up at the winged creatures and compared them to the knowledge in her head.

“Then perhaps they aren’t Winged Lizards,” Reiss said cheerfully, having overheard her voice. Aishia frowned faintly and tried to close in on him, but the other minotaurs stood in her way and rushed at her, attacking in surging waves.

However, Aishia remained calm. She purposefully leaped towards one of the minotaurs rushing at her and touched its face as she passed, instantly turning its head into a block of ice. The giant minotaur crashed to the ground immediately afterwards.

“What are you doing?”

A murky black essence had been flowing out from Reiss’s body for a while now. Aishia realized Reiss was accumulating that strange magic essence and tried to close in to stop him, but—

“I just want to drive you away and flee from this place safely.” As though to back up Reiss’s words, another breath came raining down from overhead.

“Then I’ll just reduce their numbers.”

Aishia summoned countless bullets of light around herself, then turned half of them into beams that spiraled into the skies and shot down the winged creatures. The majority of the beams made direct contact.

“Guugh?!”

The winged creatures directly hit by the beams were heavily shaken off balance, but caught themselves without falling out of the sky. It seemed like they hadn’t been damaged by anything other than the impact.

The skin of dragons and their subspecies can repel ode. Do the ones in the sky also have that characteristic?

In that case, she could either approach to physically attack them, or use her spirit arts to create a physical phenomenon. With that calm analysis, Aishia flew up and closed in on the winged creatures in the sky. However—

“I won’t let you!”

The minotaurs in the area raised their greatswords to attack Aishia as though they were reacting to Reiss’s orders.

“Doesn’t matter.” Aishia poured more magic essence into the remaining light bullets, transforming them from ten-centimeter-wide bullets to two-meter-wide ones. She then rapidly launched them at the minotaurs approaching from every direction.

“Gwuh...”

Unable to evade the shots and lacking magic-resistant skin, the minotaurs received direct damage from the bullets. Their huge bodies weighed in the tonnes, yet they were sent flying easily—some were even hit fatally and died on the spot, disintegrating into magic gems.

“As expected of a humanoid spirit—what tremendous strength.” Reiss watched Aishia fight and sighed, half in awe and half in exasperation.

“There are fewer monsters now,” Aishia said, creating several spears of ice two meters in length to snipe down the winged creatures in the sky. The number of monsters had been reduced to half of what Reiss originally summoned.

“Then let me summon them again.”

Reiss showed no sign of unease as he enlarged his shadow to call for reinforcements once more.

“Krrt, krrt...”

Skeleton warriors newly appeared from the shadow, making a rattling noise resembling chatter. There were easily over a hundred of them.

Like the minotaurs and winged creatures, they were black and looked as sinister as demons. They each had a jet-black sword and shield in hand, emitting an eerie aura.

“Are you manipulating space with that ability of yours?” Aishia asked dubiously.

The phenomenon occurring was extremely similar to space sorcery, but she couldn’t feel any ode or mana surges that normally accompanied space sorcery.

“Who knows?”

“The monsters you summon are all strange.” Aishia glanced at the skeleton army Reiss had summoned. Their auras were like monsters, but like the winged creatures, they didn’t exist within Aishia’s knowledge.

“Well, I still won’t be able to defeat you like this,” Reiss said in a defeated tone.

“Then stop resisting and give up.”

Aishia made a light sweeping motion with her arm and created a fierce gale. The wind strike created by magic essence slashed at the skeletons, mowing many of them down. However, Reiss evaded the strike by gently floating into the air.

“I was aiming for you to run out of magic essence without your contract holder around, but it seems you’re still full of energy,” he said upon landing.

Scattered around him were the skeletal remains of the warriors Aishia had defeated.

“My magic won’t run out this easily. The number of your friends has dwindled away again,” Aishia said plainly.

The minotaurs and winged creatures tried to attack her even as she was speaking, but Aishia activated her spirit arts to accurately fend them off, not even allowing them to approach.

Chapter 6: The Whereabouts of the Royal Siblings

The day after Christina and Flora were sent to the Paladia Forest, the two of them silently walked through the forest during the afternoon hours, trying to make their way out. Though they took some breaks, they had been walking continuously since morning.

Flora’s healing magic could soothe away their physical fatigue, but there was nothing that could be done about their mental fatigue. Being cornered into an extreme situation like this—on top of going through the commotion of Flora being bitten by a spider in the morning—meant they had long surpassed the limits of their minds.

“How are you holding up, Flora?” Christina asked, stopping frequently to check up on Flora as she walked behind her.

“I’m fine.” Flora nodded with a brave smile, sweating profusely.

“You’ve been staggering for a while now.”

Though they only just took a break a short moment ago.

“Ehehe... Umm, I think I may be a little hungry. It seems I don’t have much of an appetite when walking.”

“I’m sorry, I lost track of time. Let’s have lunch.”

They had been so preoccupied with walking, their sense for hunger had probably been numbed. However, they surely had to be starving—their declining ability to think was evidence of that.

“Okay.”

Though she smiled brightly, exhaustion showed on Flora’s face. Christina let Flora rest while she prepared a meal by herself.

The menu was the same as yesterday afternoon, yesterday night, and this morning—grains boiled with preserved meat into a soup seasoned with salt, along with stiff, dry bread.

It wasn’t very delicious to begin with, yet they had eaten it for four meals in a row. They were definitely bored of it by now, but they were in no position to complain.

It really makes one realize just how luxurious the food Sir Amakawa and Orphia made on our journey was.

Christina looked down at the simmering soup with conflicted thoughts, but this wasn’t the time to be lost in her sentiments. She pulled herself together and turned around to look for Flora, who was resting behind her.

“It’s almost ready, Flo... Flora?!”

She paled at the sight of her little sister wrapped in a blanket, slumped limply on the ground. Abandoning her cooking, she rushed over to her.

“Hah... Hah... Christina?” Flora replied, breathing heavily.

“What’s wrong?”

“I’m fine. I’m just a little tired.”

“But you’re sweating so much. Why are you wrapped in a blanket?”

Christina took out her handkerchief and started wiping Flora’s sweat. She then tried to lift the blanket, but—

“I’m fine. I’m just cold.”

Flora refused to let go of the blanket. She curled up into a ball, sticking only her flushed face out. Her eyes seemed to be out of focus, her pupils wavering drowsily.

“...Show me what’s under the blanket.”

Christina had a bad feeling and paused for a long moment before grabbing Flora’s hand. Then, she lifted up the blanket once again. Flora had either given up or didn’t have any energy left to object, as the blanket lifted easily.

“Ever since our last break, my neck suddenly started feeling hot... So I was casting purgo and cura underneath the blanket...” Flora explained in a faint voice. The area where she was bitten by the spider this morning had gradually turned black.

“...I’m sorry,” Christina apologized, her voice heavy with regret. She had been so desperate to leave the forest, she had failed to notice the abnormality in Flora that normally would have been evident to her.

I can’t believe we walked for hours while poison was flowing through her body...

Why didn’t Flora say anything until now? Perhaps it was because saying something wouldn’t have helped.

“Why are you apologizing, Christina? I’m the sorry one... I wasn’t actually hungry, I just wanted to rest a little...”

“Oh, goodness... What a fool. You should have just said so.” Overwhelmed by her helplessness, Christina held back her tears. She was actually calling herself a fool.

“But...”

“No buts. Can you drink water? What about food?”

“Water...”

“Here.”

She placed the cup against Flora’s mouth and let her gulp the water down.

“I’m sorry, I don’t think I can eat. Even though you went through the trouble of cooking...” Flora apologized with a pained look.

“That doesn’t matter at all. I’ll carry you from now on. We have to leave the forest as soon as possible...” The poison gnawing at Flora’s body didn’t seem to be lethal, but she didn’t feel relieved at all. They had to leave immediately.

We’ll take a little bit of food along, but we’ll have to leave the rest behind.

Christina looked around at their supplies before promptly putting out the fire heating the soup and organizing their belongings. They departed from the area soon after.

◇　◇　◇

One hour passed. Christina carried Flora on her back as she walked, hoping to leave the forest as soon as possible. It seemed like Flora was approaching her limit: her high fever had left her so exhausted, she was currently unconscious.

“Hah... Hah...” Christina panted. Her fatigue had been accumulating this entire time, but now she was carrying another person through the uneven forest on top of that.

Since her high heels weren’t suitable for walking, she had thrown them away. Walking barefoot meant she stepped on rocks and twigs that injured her, making her feet bleed and protest in pain.

The air in the forest was cool, but the constant walking left her body flushed hot. She was also sweating a lot, making her dress stick to her uncomfortably. With Flora and her high fever being carried on her back, the fabric there was completely soaked.

However, Christina didn’t begrudge that in the slightest as she walked. She didn’t slow down her pace at all. In fact, whenever she felt like she was struggling, she sped up as though to scold herself for it.

Rio observed every small move Lucius made so that he could react if he tried to harm Christina and Flora. Then, Lucius suddenly hugged Christina towards him, Flora still on her back.

“Eep...!” Christina let out a shriek as she lost balance. Meanwhile, Lucius took his gaze off Rio and looked into the distance. Immediately after that, Lucius, Christina, and Flora disappeared.

“What?!” The one who raised his voice in confusion was Duran, who had been silent until now. He was astonished by Lucius’s sudden disappearance, but—

Over there!

Rio was able to identify Lucius’s location with precision. He could see someone falling from the sky several meters away, as though he had teleported there.

However, Rio wasn’t about to lose to that. He used his wind spirit arts to forcefully accelerate his body and approach Lucius.

“Eek!”

Lucius grabbed the fabric of Christina’s dress and threw her and Flora together towards the ground. The fabric at the middle of the back of her dress ripped loudly. There was no way she’d walk away unharmed after falling several dozen meters.

“Tch...” Rio manipulated the wind to super forcefully change his direction, accelerate, and catch the falling Christina and Flora. He then landed on the ground with the two of them.

“Protect them if you can.” Lucius stood behind Rio, his sword swinging down from overhead.

He’s so fast! Wait, this is—

Rio hugged Christina and Flora close to him as he parried the blow one-handedly with his sword. But even he couldn’t handle that much—his balance was completely thrown off, and he could barely manage to parry the attack.

“Hey, what’s the matter? Huh?! Your movements have dulled!” Lucius swung his sword without a care.

“Guh...” With Christina and Flora embraced in his grasp, Rio stood his ground to fight back, but he was at too much of a disadvantage. Even Christina could tell that just by looking.

“Sir Amakawa, you can throw me aside!” Christina twisted her body around to plead at him in a panic.

“It’s dangerous, so please stay still. Keep a tight hold of Princess Flora and don’t let go of me!” Rio ordered, hugging Christina even closer.

“Your back’s wide open!”

Lucius suddenly disappeared from before Rio. In the next moment, he was standing diagonally behind him, swinging his sword at his back. However, as though predicting that move, Rio charged forward with Christina embraced in one arm. Lucius’s sword cut through empty space at the last moment.

He really is teleporting after all. The last time we fought, he also moved as though he was teleporting, but he didn’t base his fight around this ability. Is it the power of his sword? Or does it have something to do with his eye? There’s quite a lot of magic essence flowing from it...

Rio evaded the attacks while analyzing the situation with precision. He surmised that the reason why it seemed like Lucius had teleported was probably because he really had teleported.

In reality, he’d been able to predict Lucius’s warp destination just now by feeling the fluctuation of ode and mana around him. But it was still an extremely troublesome ability—he wouldn’t be able to let Christina and Flora escape somewhere safe like this. Thanks to that, Rio was unable to separate from the two of them, which made it impossible for him to move at high speeds.

This made close combat rather difficult, as Lucius was able to move freely by teleporting around. His prospects were far too poor like this...which was why Rio decided to discard his hand. He gathered the essence within him and stomped against the ground.

A two-meter-wide circle of earth underneath Rio and Christina’s feet protruded from the ground, lifting them ten meters into the air.

“Huh?” The sudden floating sensation had Christina shell-shocked. She was tremendously confused by the sight of the ground beneath her feet rising like a living tower.

“Impudent brat!” Lucius swung his sword diagonally upwards from the ground.

The black blade of his sword released a pitch-black strike, severing the earth tower Rio had created at the base.

Rio put essence into his feet and leaped off the tower before it crumbled. Immediately after, the earth tower that had acted as his foothold fell apart into rectangular blocks that floated in the air.

Wh-What’s happening? What’s the meaning of this? Are we floating as well?!

Christina glanced around in a panic, looking at the blocks floating in the air and themselves in mute amazement.

No one had uttered any spells to activate magic until now, yet all kinds of supernatural phenomena kept happening one after another. Her surprise was only natural.

Meanwhile, Rio looked down at Lucius on the ground and pointed his sword at him. No sooner had he done so than the group of blocks floating in the air all started falling towards the ground at a rapid speed. No, it was like they had been fired by an invisible power.

If each block weighed several kilograms, they should make quite the impact by the time they fell to the ground. In reality, the blocks that crashed into the ground created small craters and dust clouds.

Wh-What is that? What’s happening? Is Sir Amakawa using the ability of his enchanted sword? But wasn’t his enchanted sword a wind sword?

Christina could no longer keep up with the situation. However, Flora had once witnessed Rio fight using spirit arts, so she wasn’t as surprised as her older sister. Still suffering from the poison, her expression was dazed as she looked down at the ground.

But, just then—

Boom!

A tremendous explosion roared from behind Christina and Flora.

Wh-What?!

Christina whipped around in confusion. There stood Lucius, who should have been on the ground, with his sword held overhead.

“Tch...”

And yet, he was unable to slash Christina and Flora in the back. Rio had created a barrier of magic essence to block Lucius’s sword. Still, a single blow from Lucius’s blade had enough force to crack the barrier...

At any rate, Lucius’s attack was blocked, making him click his tongue in irritation. Christina and Flora could also see the faint light wall blocking Lucius’s sword from reaching him. They also knew that it was Rio who had put up the barrier, though they hadn’t seen him do so.

“Now it’s my turn,” Rio said, summoning orbs of light several centimeters wide around him. Of course, Lucius had no intention of just taking the hit and disappeared on the spot.

But Rio was able to predict where Lucius would move to with a high degree of precision. He fired the orbs at the area on the ground where he foresaw Lucius appearing. There were about a hundred or so orbs of light that orbited in the air before falling to the ground. In addition, Rio made full use of his tremendous magic essence to continuously create more orbs, firing them at the ground. It almost looked like a meteor shower of light orbs.

Wh-What? What is this, really...? Christina became even more confused.

At the Royal Academy, Rio had been mocked as a failure for being unable to make a contract with magic. And yet, now he could create magical phenomena without even chanting a spell... He was even flying in the air, with no sign of falling anytime soon.

The rain of light orbs Rio was firing each had the might of a lower-grade spell, but together they were an overwhelming threat. And he was firing them a hundred at a time towards the ground every few seconds. Did he have an endless amount of essence? The scale of the phenomenon being created was greater than advanced magic—it was practically on par with the highest grade of attack magic possible.

However, Lucius was also impressive. He dashed about the ground, swinging his sword to cut down the light orbs while evading the rain of attacks. He sometimes disappeared and reappeared in a different position in the distance.

After a while, Lucius came to a stop and looked up at Rio floating in the air. Suddenly, a voice sounded from above their heads.

“Here, you can have these back.”

Lucius was looking down from ten meters above Rio’s head, pointing the tip of his sword at him. Immediately after, several hundred orbs of light surrounded Rio in every direction.

Did he absorb my light bullets to use himself?

Rio immediately deduced that there was no possible escape route and poured essence into his sword. He created a storm to blow the orbs away, forcibly making a hole in the encirclement. He then tried to escape through it.

“I won’t let you!” Lucius teleported to cut into Rio’s exit route. He poured magic essence into his sword to stock up dark energy and strike Rio with it.

However, Rio also poured essence into his sword to counter Lucius’s attack with a blast of wind. Their respective energies clashed, forming a tremendous shock wave.

What a fight this is...

Christina had been desperately clinging to Rio with Flora in her arms for some time now, watching the battle that she couldn’t believe was happening between two humans. Flora seemed to be having a tough time being moved around midair so much, as her feverish eyes were unable to stay focused.

“Damn it...” While Lucius could teleport, he wasn’t able to fly—the shock wave from his attack hitting Rio’s sent him falling down. The fact he wasn’t able to defeat Rio despite his favorable position made his brow furrow in frustration as he teleported straight to the ground.

Rio also lowered his altitude, glaring at Lucius as he descended. Once he landed, about ten meters of ground lifted up in square tiles.

“Wha...?!” The sudden spectacle left Christina speechless once more.

The tiles that lifted up blocked their view of Lucius before them—in fact, they collapsed over him, crushing him underneath.

However, Lucius teleported to evade the attack, moving out of the range of the tiles that lifted up and fell—based on his original position, he had moved horizontally to the side.

He didn’t teleport through the wall... That confirms it. Lucius’s teleportation ability only allows him to move where his left eye can see.

Using the attack just now, Rio was able to confirm what he had noticed while firing the orbs of light at Lucius from above.

“Tch...” Lucius clicked his tongue in annoyance.

“Is Princess Flora all right?” Rio suddenly asked Christina, who now stood beside him. Dazed, she snapped back to her senses and answered him in an apologetic tone.

“Y-Yes... Umm. To be honest, she’s not in the best condition. She’s been poisoned with a toxin that couldn’t be treated with magic.”

“I see. Then we shouldn’t move her around too much,” Rio said, staring at Lucius standing ten or so meters before them.

There’s no doubt that Lucius’s enchanted sword can control space. His main powers are the ability to teleport short distances visible to his left eye, and the ability to absorb spirit arts and fire them back. He hasn’t used it yet this match, but he can also open a hole in space and thrust his sword through it like last time. That essence-engulfed left arm of his must also have some kind of trick to it...

Rio recalled their fight thus far and analyzed the ability of Lucius’s enchanted sword. Those were the highlights he had to be careful of.

Just then, Lucius transferred his sword from his right hand to his left hand.

He switched his sword to his left hand? Wasn’t he right-handed?

He had always fought with his right hand until now. Rio grew more wary of Lucius’s left arm.

“There’s one thing I find incomprehensible,” Lucius suddenly said to Rio.

“...” Rio watched him silently.

“Be it your spirit arts, swordsmanship, or martial arts—where did you learn all of it?”

“Who knows?”

“You’re far too proficient in your movements. Even if you have talent, there’s a crazy amount of experience behind your skills. It’s not something a brat in his teens should be capable of. Supposing that you learned your swordcraft during your childhood, you would have learned it from the Royal Academy in Beltrum—but those movements aren’t the Beltrum Kingdom style.”

“...They’re my own style.”

“Your own style? Well, whatever. It’s time for round two—a fresh start. Unfortunately, however, I’m right-handed. I may not be able to go as easy on you with my left arm, so don’t hold it against me.” Despite his clear suspicion at Rio’s answer, Lucius dismissed the matter and checked his grip on the sword clutched in his left hand.

The left arm is the one I burned away without a trace in the last match. It must have been regenerated through some kind of forbidden technique along with that left eye...

The fact he switched his sword meant the ability couldn’t be activated unless the sword was in his left hand.

“Wh...?!”

Suddenly, Lucius swung his sword ten-odd meters in front of Rio, but the blade of the sword had disappeared and was closing in from behind. Rio promptly held his sword ready behind his back and caught the blow. The sound of clashing metal screeched, surprising Christina into looking for the source of the sound. When she spotted the blade that had warped through space to float in the air, she broke out in a cold sweat.

“Ha! So you’ll react to this attack like it’s nothing as well, huh? Come to think of it, I’ve used this move once before the last time we fought. But...” Lucius said unhappily as Rio thought to himself.

If he can use that attack just now without any restriction, it might be a little risky trying to do this while protecting two other people.

Rio felt a sharp pang of danger—and that danger had already approached. Another sharp clashing screech echoed.

“Huh...?”

Christina looked in the direction of the sound. This time it didn’t come from behind Rio, but Christina. Rio had gone around her to catch the blow—even though Lucius was still standing over ten meters away. Then, at the next metallic clash in succession, she finally understood. Once again, although Lucius was before them, this time it came from the left of Flora...

...Is he warping just the blade of his sword using space sorcery?

The reality was exactly as it appeared, and Christina was filled with terror the moment she understood it.

“I knew it—you can tell where my attacks are coming from, can’t you? Cheeky bastard. But this isn’t all I’ve got—thanks to the left arm you lopped off, I can use my sword even better than before. Here, let’s turn up the pace,” Lucius said, then resumed swinging his sword. One swing, then another, followed by one more—all at different angles and speeds.

Clang, clang, clang. The sound of swords clashing gradually got faster. Rio saw through Lucius’s attacks and knocked back all the blows, but he was treading on thin ice doing so.

“...” Christina was frozen stiff. All she was doing was standing, yet she felt closer to death than living. The attacks seemingly came from nowhere, but Rio blocked them all for her—that was the only thing keeping her alive.

This made it even harder for Rio to leave Christina and Flora. The moment he did, the two of them were as good as dead.

“Don’t worry. Simply slashing from afar isn’t artistic enough for my tastes. I’ll come closer, then,” Lucius said, using his teleportation to warp behind Christina and Flora. By the time he finished warping, he had already made a stabbing motion.

Rio immediately cut between Lucius and the princesses, but the distance to Lucius was oddly far.

Oh no!

Rio hurried back to his original position as soon as he realized why. The next moment, the blade of the sword Lucius held came flying. If Rio hadn’t returned, it would have pierced through Christina’s body, but—

“Guh...”

Though it had only been a moment, that moment cost Rio everything. He was unable to block the attack successfully and took the blade in his left arm.

“S-Sir Amakawa?!” Christina paled. It was clear that he had been stabbed in order to protect her.

“Right, your clothes do seem worn out. But I’m not a noble.”

“O-Oh, I see.”

“By the way, what are you doing here?” Renji asked the slightly sullen girl.

When the girl realized Renji wasn’t a noble, she relaxed her guard and sighed lightly. With her shifted attitude, she questioned him in a less formal manner. “That’s what I should be asking... Haha. Who are you, anyway?”

“I’m a traveler.”

“A traveler...” The girl shot Renji a dubious look.

“There’s no need to be suspicious of me. I’m not here to do anything bad.”

“Hmm... So what do you want from our village? Oh, are you here because you saw the pillar of light?” The girl still looked at Renji distrustfully, but then she thought of a possible reason why Renji came to visit and asked about it.

“The pillar of light?” Renji tilted his head.

“It disappeared right away, but there was an amazing pillar of light in the sky just now.”

“Ah... that light. Right. I saw that from a distance and wandered in this direction. I didn’t really have a destination, so I followed the light.” Renji quick-wittedly matched his story with her words.

“I knew it. If it’s the pillar of light you’re after, it came from the forest. Everyone in the village was shocked and made a commotion about it. Some people went into the forest to investigate, but they should be back soon,” the girl explained excitedly.

Based on the situation, the center of the crater where I stood would have been the point of the light pillar, right? So that light was what summoned me into this world.

“I see.” Renji nodded as he analyzed the situation in his head.

“If you want to hear more about it, I can show you to the chief,” the girl offered kindly.

“No... I’m interested in that too, but I have another favor to ask.”

“A favor?”

“I don’t have anywhere to go. Could I stay in this village?”

“Huh...?”

“Could I? Otherwise I’d have to sleep outside.”

“I’d have to ask the village chief.”

“Please ask him, then.”

“Huh? Why me? I’ll show you the way to the chief, so you ask him.” The girl frowned.

“Fine. I have to do it, I guess,” Renji agreed with a shrug.

What a weird guy. His hair color is also...not quite strange, but black isn’t a color I’ve ever seen in this village. His face isn’t quite girlish, but rather childlike? Still, he’s cocky and shameless. I guess all boys are like this, though. The girl’s childhood friend came to mind as she compared Renji’s attitude to his, making her sigh quietly.

“Let’s go, then,” she prompted.

“All right.”

“By the way, what’s your name?”

“...It’s Renji.”

When the girl asked for his name, Renji hesitated before answering. The reason why his reply was delayed was because he feared giving his Japanese name would sound questionable. However, Renji was a name that passed even overseas, so he figured he could use it openly here.

“I see. My name’s Rhea. Nice to meet you.”

This was how Renji and Rhea first met.

◇　◇　◇

That night, at Rhea’s home...

“Ugh, why does he have to stay here? I’m a single young woman, living alone...” Rhea muttered to herself with her lips in a pout as she cooked in the kitchen.

“You’re the one who agreed,” Renji said awkwardly.

“Honestly, why did I agree?”

Rhea had shown Renji to the village chief, but he had expressed his disapproval in providing accommodation.

“Seriously though. Who are you?”

“I said I was a wandering traveler.”

“That’s so shady...”

Renji refused to explain his background properly. Because he was trying to hide his summoning into this world, he couldn’t help his lack of background, but as a result, all the villagers—including the chief—looked at him with a distrustful gaze.

If he wasn’t a noble, why did he have such clean clothes? If he was a traveler like he claimed, why didn’t he have a sword on him? Why was he traveling without any money or tools? On top of that, he wanted them to show him to the nearest city.

“Well it’s the truth, so I can’t help it,” Renji had boldly declared, leaving a bad impression on the village chief. He had expressed his displeasure in letting an unknown outsider stay in the village.

But the one who had stopped the chief was Rhea. “The nights are cold; it’d be too pitiful to make him camp outside...” were the words that started an argument between her and the chief about how “this man doesn’t have any manners,” and “that doesn’t mean we can let him sleep outside,” and so on.

In the end, the chief had said, “If you’re that insistent, then host him in your own house. I’ll allow that much.” And with Rhea’s permission, it was decided he would stay at her place.

“Well, I’m grateful I don’t have to sleep outside. Sorry...” Renji apologized awkwardly, feeling bad for everything he had done.

“It’s fine. But you’re leaving the next time a merchant comes, got it?” Rhea stressed. Renji was staying at her house under the condition that he would leave with the next merchant that came by the village, which was at most one month away.

“Yeah, I know. In exchange for staying here, I’ll help out with whatever work I can.”

“That goes without saying,” Rhea snorted. She turned back to her cooking and said curtly, “I’ve left a change of clothes out, so use the ones I put over there.”

“You live alone because your parents died, right? Whose clothes are these?” Renji asked.

“My late older brother,” Rhea answered smoothly.

“Hmm... I see.” Renji was taken aback, but he didn’t know how to react, so he lightly brushed it off.

“...” Rhea said nothing more than that, silently working away at cooking. Thus began Renji and Rhea’s temporary life together.

◇　◇　◇

Late that night, when the villagers had all fallen fast asleep...

“Mm...” Renji was sleeping on the bed that Rhea had lent him. He was dreaming, yet his consciousness was stirred completely.

Where am I...?

Before he knew it, he was in a pure white room. The room continued endlessly.

(Hero.)

An unfamiliar male voice suddenly echoed in Renji’s head.

Who’s there?! Renji looked around with a gasp.

(Hero. The chosen hero.)

Hero...? Does he mean me?

(I impart upon you the knowledge of how to use the Divine Arms of Ice you have been bestowed. Accept it.)

What? Wha...?!

In the next moment, knowledge burst into Renji’s head. It was knowledge about tools called the Divine Arms, which he had never heard of before. All of a sudden, he understood what Divine Arms were, what they could do, and even how to use them.

This is... Renji was taken aback in his dream.

(Divine Arms will respond to your requests, granting you power. You are a hero. You are a special, chosen existence. Know that.)

Gah! What the hell is that?! Who are you?! This is so one-sided! Renji questioned the owner of the voice.

The owner of the voice spoke to Renji with no acknowledgment of the other. There was no conversation to be held. And then—

(This is my final advice to you. Until the day comes: survive.)

The owner of the voice left behind those words and faded from Renji’s consciousness.

H-Hey, wait! Did you leave?! Who are you?! Are you the one who brought me to this world? Why did you do that?! Renji called in a hurry, but there was no response. In the next moment, Renji jerked awake.

“Ah?!”

His heart was pounding, possibly out of excitement. “Hah... Hah... Was it... a dream? No...” Renji gulped.

Imagine it. The Divine Arms I’ve obtained.

According to the information in his head, the Divine Arms would materialize in the shape of the weapon imagined by its wielder. Renji closed his eyes and focused his mind, thrusting out his right hand.

After a moment, faint light particles floated in the air, gathering together in the next instant to form a halberd in his hand. It was taller than Renji’s height, with an intricate and artistic design.

“I did it...” Renji grinned. “According to what I learned, this Divine Arms wields the power of ice. Apparently if I name it, my impression of it will strengthen and speed up the materialization... Ice, huh? Then maybe... Cocytus.”

Cocytus was the name of the icy world in the final layer of hell. Though he kept it a secret from the people around him, Renji was actually a nerd when it came to things like that, so he had an abundant amount of useless knowledge.

“Disappear.”

Cocytus vanished in an instant.

“Okay, it’s gone. Cocytus.”

This time he tried to materialize it. Perhaps it was because he had named it, but there was practically no time lag at all.

“It feels familiar in my hand. It isn’t heavy at all. Looks like it was true that my body and physical abilities were enhanced as well.”

The halberd was roughly two meters long. He didn’t know what material it was made of, but it was a metal object that should weigh pretty heftily. However, for some reason, it felt like he could handle it freely.

“I want to try swinging it...” Renji couldn’t help the desire within him to test swing Cocytus. He had the eager expression of someone who had just bought a new game to play.

“Maybe I can sneak out quietly and try...”

The villagers were all asleep, including his housemate. They shouldn’t notice if he snuck out of the house. With that thought, Renji slipped out of Rhea’s home.

The full moon is almost here. I should be able to walk in this darkness.

There were no lights leaking from any of the houses, so the villagers must have all been sound asleep. The only source of light was the moon, but the rod cell of the human eye could see clearly enough under the moonlight without any street lamps.

The region Renji lived in in Japan had been surrounded by farmland without man-made lights as well, so he wasn’t afraid of this much darkness.

“This far should be fine.” Renji arrived at a location far enough to oversee the houses of the village and began spending a few minutes doing some light stretches to relax his body’s muscles. Then—

“Cocytus.” He called the name of the Divine Arms he had vanished earlier and materialized it in his hand. Then he tried holding it in a stance with both hands.

“I don’t know if this is the right grip to use, but... Hah!” Renji relied on the strength of his enhanced body to swing Cocytus horizontally with all his might.

“Hmm... Mmph! Hah!” He swung the halberd a second and third time to grasp the feeling of it.

“I see.” Renji grinned smugly and began to swing the Divine Arms silently. Horizontally, vertically down, vertically up, rotating it over his head... He nimbly performed all the tricky movements he considered to look cool. It was a feat no normal person could do. After that, he switched from a two-handed hold to a one-handed hold, swinging Cocytus many times to draw the path that he wanted.

“I’ve got the feel of it now.” He swung the halberd down one last time, stopping barely before scraping the ground. He then lifted it up and rested the handle against his right shoulder, laughing.

“Still, I’ve been swinging such a huge thing around so dramatically and I’m still not out of breath. Makes sense since I’m in another world, huh?”

Thanks to all the other-world novels and stories he had read while obsessed with the subgenre, Renji was somehow able to accept the situation he had been left in fairly smoothly. However, since he didn’t know anything about how to return to Earth at the moment, he still had his concerns.

“...Time to go back, I guess.”

Renji looked up at the sky, lost in thought, before returning to Rhea’s house.

◇　◇　◇

The next morning, during breakfast...

“Say, Rhea.”

“What?”

“Do you know about the heroes?” Renji asked.

“I do, but... Are you making fun of me for being from the country?” Rhea had an exasperated expression, as though there was no way she wouldn’t know.

“No, that wasn’t my intention...” Renji scratched his cheek, frowning.

“We hear about them in fairy tales, so even children know about them. They’re the disciples of the Six Wise Gods that saved the world, right?”

“Yeah, that’s right... I was just wondering if there was any disparity with the fairy tales that I know of. I’m curious. What are the fairy tales told in this village like?” Renji asked, immediately adjusting his words to fit her reply.

Rhea looked up at the ceiling to recall her memories of the story. “Hmm. I doubt there’d be much difference, but... It’s a long story, so to summarize, an evil demon king that could control monsters appeared a thousand years ago. In order to save the world, the Six Wise Gods imparted wisdom upon us humans. The fight with the demons intensified, so the Six Wise Gods summoned six heroes from the world of the gods for the sake of humanity. The heroes could cut down thousands of monsters in a single swing. The Six Wise Gods and the heroes worked together to defeat the demon army, bringing peace to the world. And they all lived happily ever after. Sound familiar to you?”

“I see. It isn’t any different to the story I know, then.”

“Well, it is a story written in the holy scriptures. If anyone tried to twist the truth, they’d be declared a heretic and denounced.”

“Yeah, that’s right.” Heroes were religious beings, apparently.

If it’s knowledge even a child would know, then I can’t ask too many questions about it. Otherwise my lack of knowledge would be exposed. With that thought—

“Do you think heroes exist?” Renji asked.

“They’re the great heroes of legend, so it’d be a huge deal if they appeared, don’t you think?” Rhea answered with an amused laugh.

“Right, of course. And even if they did appear, it’s unlikely anyone would believe them,” Renji muttered meaningfully, then spoke nothing more about heroes to Rhea after that.

◇　◇　◇

Five days had passed since Renji arrived in this world.

He was getting used to life in Rhea’s home, but he still didn’t fit in in the village. He had completely familiarized himself to life in Rhea’s home, but the villagers all gave him the cold shoulder for being a suspicious outsider.

He was treated like an enemy by Rhea’s childhood friend more so than anyone else; he was a boy who came up to him the day after he first stayed at her house and demanded he leave the village. At that time, Rhea stood on Renji’s side while acting as the mediator, which caused Renji to smirk and send the childhood friend flying into a rage. Renji had immediately enhanced his body with the power of his Divine Arms to evade all of the boy’s punches easily, continuing until the boy ran out of stamina to move. It was barely even a match.

Some villagers who witnessed that scene feared Renji’s strength, spreading rumors until Renji became completely isolated.

The villagers had no ill feelings towards Rhea, but they didn’t try to approach her while she was with Renji. On top of staying at her house, he always went with her to her work outside, so an uncomfortable atmosphere surrounded the village.

“Your childhood friend was glaring at me again,” Renji said to Rhea over dinner.

“After what you did, that’s only natural,” Rhea snapped.

“Just so you know, what I did was legitimate self-defense,” Renji said calmly.

It would be more accurate to say that he had purposefully created a situation where his act of self-defense would be seen as legitimate, but Renji didn’t have the faintest intention of showing mercy to someone so hostile towards him, so it was really nothing more than an act of revenge. Rhea hadn’t seen the provoking smirk he had sent towards her childhood friend.

“But with your strength, wouldn’t you have been able to pin Yoran down easily?” Rhea inquired indirectly.

“Don’t be silly. I didn’t have the leisure to do something like that. Your childhood friend is the strongest person in this village, no? I’m a lot shorter than him, too.”

“That’s true, but...”

At the time, Renji had seemed unusually happy about being attacked by Yoran. In reality, Renji wanted to test how his physical body enhancement would fare against Yoran, so the impression Rhea received wasn’t mistaken.

However, Rhea didn’t think Renji was a bad guy. He was blunt and uncommunicative, and sometimes spoke with an arrogant attitude, but actually living with him made her notice his unexpectedly kind side. He carried the heavy things for her when she was at work, and he also helped out around the house. The other men in the village lacked such consideration.

“Is that guy in love with you?” Renji asked, watching Rhea for her reaction.

“Huh? What are you on about?”

“He got real worked up over you. That’s why I was wondering if he was.”

“Please. We’re just childhood friends. He’s been foul-mouthed towards me since before you came to this village. I have no idea why he’s so mad about it now,” Rhea said with a tired sigh.

“Hmm. Then are you in love with him?” No matter how Renji looked at it, it was clear that the boy had a crush on her, but he decided not to point that out.

“...You must be kidding me. Do you want to get punched?”

“I see.”

Rhea had sent a fierce glare at him, but Renji merely brushed it off with a cheery laugh.

“It’s not like anyone will want to marry me. I’m doomed to grow old alone in this lonely house,” Rhea said sulkingly.

“Eh, you can do housework well. I’m sure there are plenty of people out there who would want you as a bride. Your face isn’t too bad either,” Renji muttered.

“H-Huh...?! What are you saying?!” Rhea blinked several times before turning red.

“I just said what I was thinking.”

“But you said you think my face isn’t too bad... Does that mean you think I’m cute?” Rhea stared at Renji with a faint blush on her cheeks.

“Now, as you are aware, I’m a wanderer... An immigrant, basically. I haven’t had many women around me before, and I haven’t seen the faces of the women in other villages, so I cannot give an objective opinion.” Renji averted his eyes and dodged the question. He had attended an all-boys middle school and high school, so he felt some charm from the reluctantly caring Rhea. Perhaps that was why he had said something in praise of her, but couldn’t be frank and call her cute to her face.

“I’m asking what you think right now, though.”

“I just said it. Your face isn’t too bad.”

“That phrasing...” Rhea pouted, glaring at Renji scornfully.

“What?” Renji turned away and asked.

“You’re always so arrogant, Renji. That’s why you end up antagonizing everyone in the village,” Rhea pointed out frankly.

“Me? The arrogant ones are the villagers. Especially the village chief and your childhood friend.”

“I won’t deny that. But you also have a condescending attitude when you speak sometimes. When you went to ask to stay in this village, things would have gone better if you had explained things before making your request. We’ve had lots of travelers stay in the village in the past.”

“But they were also given the cold shoulder by the villagers for being outsiders too, no?”

“Well, we did keep our distance to watch what they did, but no one actively avoided them like they do with you right now.”

“...” Renji fell silent.

“I know you’re not a bad guy, so I bet they’d change their minds if they had the opportunity to do so,” Rhea said, watching Renji once again.

“Is there a need to change their minds?”

“You said you were a wanderer, but do you have a goal for your journey?” Rhea responded to Renji’s question with one of her own.

Renji thought for a moment before replying. “No... Not in particular.”

“Hmm... Then how about you live in this village for a while?” Rhea suddenly suggested.

“...I’ll see.” Renji evaded the question.

“I think you’d be a great help to the village if you stayed. You’re strong.”

“The villagers already dislike having an outsider stay here temporarily. It’d be even worse if I settled here.”

“That’s not true. We’ve had people move into the village before. People will change when they’re given the right opportunity to do so.”

“I wonder about that. Plus, I don’t have anywhere to live.”

“...You can just keep living here.”

“Wasn’t the agreement that I could only stay until the next traveling merchant comes?”

In other words, it could be a month at the longest, or as early as tomorrow. Renji looked at Rhea in slight surprise.

“If you insisted on staying in this village, then I wouldn’t mind, you know? It gets boring living in this house by myself, and it’s a little scary at night. I’m the only one in this village that lives alone, too...”

“Are you lonely?” Renji asked, watching Rhea’s expression.

“Not exactly lonely, but...having someone to talk to and eat meals with in the house has just been kind of nice, that’s all,” Rhea mumbled.

Perhaps that was why the living arrangements she had been so against in the beginning didn’t seem so bad anymore. She no longer had to watch the other villagers returning to their families at the end of the workday with envy. “Don’t you get lonely traveling alone, Renji?” Rhea asked cautiously.

“I...” Renji stumbled over his words in thought. It was a lie that he traveled alone. However, he could understand how it felt to be alone. In reality, he did find living together with Rhea in this tiny home a lot more fun than when he stayed shut inside his room whenever he wasn’t at school. There was a part of him that agreed with her.

“But isn’t it problematic for an unmarried young man and woman to live together for real? Our current living arrangement is questionable enough...” Renji expressed his hesitation, asking his question in an inarticulate manner.

“Shall we just get married, then?”

“...It’s been five days since we met. Right?” Renji said awkwardly, his eyes widening. He was fairly shocked.

“...R-Right. It’s all because you said such weird things to begin with. Calling me cute and all that.” Rhea collected herself and spoke with a bright-red face.

“I don’t recall calling you cute...”

Renji trailed off, unable to give a clear denial. After wandering into another world and living together with a girl, his mood had been in high spirits without his realization. In his ten-odd years of life, he had never experienced the feeling of being wanted by anyone other than his family, so Rhea’s feelings echoed deeply in his heart.

◇　◇　◇

The next afternoon, Renji and Rhea took a break from their work and returned home to have lunch, when a visitor appeared.

“Hey, Rhea. Come with me.”

It was Rhea’s childhood friend, Yoran. Yoran walked to the dining table and shot a glare at Renji before ignoring him in favor of talking to Rhea.

“What do you want?”

“The village chief is calling for you. He has something important to discuss about the future of the village.”

“The village chief...? What do you mean by ‘important’?” Rhea asked, eyeing him warily.

“I can’t tell you in front of the outsider,” Yoran answered, aware of Renji’s presence.

“...Does that mean it involves Renji?” Rhea asked sullenly.

“H-How would I know? I was just told to bring you there,” Yoran said, his tone harsh out of awkwardness.

“Go on, Rhea. Don’t worry about me.”

Renji smirked at Yoran in a relaxed manner while speaking to Rhea.

“Fine...”

Rhea seemed unhappy with being called out for an unclear reason, reluctantly nodding her head only after hearing Renji’s words.

“Grr... Come.”

Yoran clenched his fists and left the house. Rhea followed after him, heading towards the village chief’s house.

◇　◇　◇

Yoran brought Rhea to the village chief’s house.

“What did you want to discuss, ch...”

Rhea spotted the village chief as soon as she entered the house and started to question why she was summoned in an aggressive tone. However, she trailed off mid-sentence. There were people who weren’t from the village in the house—a total of eight people. They were all armed and dressed in expensive-looking military uniforms. The most well-dressed among them was a plump man positioned at the head of the room.

“Are you the girl living with the man named Renji?” The plump man in a military uniform glared at Rhea.

“U-Umm...” Rhea was completely bewildered.

“Answer the question. Are you the girl living with the man called Renji?” the plump man said in a threatening tone.

“E-Eek!”

He was a noble. Once Rhea sensed the other party’s social status, she nodded her head in fear.

“I’m going to question you about that man. Answer with everything you know.”

After the plump man spoke again, he asked Rhea question after question. Things like, was his hair really black, did he make any ideological statements, where did you meet Renji, do you know the reason why he came to this village, did he say anything regarding the lake in the forest, and so on. Rhea answered each and every question honestly.

“I see. So you don’t know anything useful. In that case, I have no choice but to investigate him directly.” The plump noble sighed in annoyance.

“U-Umm, why are you investigating Renji?” Rhea could easily predict that Renji was the “him” the noble was referring to, so she questioned the reason why nervously.

“The lake near this village completely dried up. That lake was one of the holy grounds of this kingdom, and that man named Renji is suspected of drying up that lake. If this is the truth, then it is a crime deserving of capital punishment,” the plump nobleman said.

“P-Please wait a moment! Renji wouldn’t do such a thing...!”

There was no way he would do that.

“That’s what I’m investigating. Let’s go. Lead the way, chief.”

“Y-Yes, sir.”

The nobleman turned a deaf ear and stood up, leaving with the knights in the room.

Wh-What should I do...?

Rhea watched their retreating backs in horror before snapping back to her senses and following them.

◇　◇　◇

Several minutes later, at Rhea’s house...

From the entrance, she could see Renji seated opposite to the plump nobleman at the back of the house. Two knights stood behind the noble, and Rhea stood farther behind them by the entrance. There were more knights on standby outside Rhea’s house, along with a gathering of curious villagers.

“What’s the meaning of this?” Renji asked unhappily, glaring at the noble and knights who had barged into the house.

“Your name is Renji, correct? The one who came to this village six days ago?”

“So what if I am?” Renji’s attitude didn’t change even when he was in front of nobility. He questioned the noble in return with an equal way of speaking.

The man furrowed his brows in displeasure as he spoke. “I am an interrogator of the Vilkis Kingdom. I was dispatched here from the capital in order to investigate the pillar of light that appeared six days ago. After questioning the villagers, I’ve determined that you are under suspicion of drying up the nearby lake in the forest.”

Renji paused for a moment, feigning ignorant composure. “...What are you talking about?”

“That lake was a holy ground of the kingdom. Six days ago, on the day you came to this village, a pillar of light rose into the sky. Was that something you were involved in? The drying up of the lake was your doing, was it not?”

“You’re suspecting me of that without any proof whatsoever?”

It seemed that the villagers had passed on information about him after the nobles arrived in the village. Renji came to that conclusion and sought the disclosure of evidence.

“I am not required to show you anything. What was your purpose in visiting this village?”

“In that case, I’m not required to tell you anything.”

Renji gave a scornful smile as payback. This made the nobleman frown openly.

At this rate, Renji would incur the noble’s displeasure and be killed. Rhea was pale-faced as she peeked through the entryway and called out to Renji. “Renji! This is a nobleman you’re speaking to! Apologize immediately or you’ll be killed!”

“I have nothing to apologize for,” Renji replied sullenly.

“I don’t care if you don’t answer. You will be sent to an appropriate location for the crime of drying up the lake,” the nobleman stated coldly.

“I didn’t do it,” Renji insisted firmly.

“In that case, you can prove that by answering my questions. If a suspicious person with an unfamiliar hair color and unusual clothing visits a village immediately after a pillar of light rises into the sky, it’s only natural to feel a certain amount of distrust, don’t you think? You claimed to be a traveler, yet you were practically bare-handed. You said you lost your belongings, but where did you lose them?”

The nobleman didn’t lose his temper over Renji’s impolite attitude, instead observing him closely as he asked his questions in a flat tone.

“I came to the village from the road opposite to the forest. I literally went through the gate on that side and ran into Rhea in the farmlands there. I didn’t go near the forest. My belongings were lost somewhere along that road. Since I lost them, I obviously don’t remember where.”

It seemed that Renji couldn’t stand the current situation, as he spoke firmly.

“Hmm. If it’s the road opposite to the forest, then you mean to say you came from the western road? That means you may have lost your belongings in the valley a short distance down the road. That area is rocky and difficult to walk on,” the plump noble guessed as though he was in deep thought.

“Yeah, that’s right,” Renji declared immediately.

“Hmm... That’s strange. Very strange. I remembered things wrongly just now, and there shouldn’t be any valley down the west road at all.” The nobleman narrowed his eyes.

“What...?” Renji’s face froze.

The nobleman suddenly adopted a serious expression. “Did you really come to the village from the west road?”

“...” Renji’s gaze wavered as he fell silent.

“Why did you lie? Where did you come from? You really were in the forest, weren’t you? You must know something about the lake drying up—or perhaps you are the perpetrator behind it...” After concluding that Renji had been lying, the interrogator looked at him sharply. As expected of an interrogator, a mere high school student like Renji became cornered easily.

“...I don’t know anything.” Renji shook his head, faltering.

“Do you think the words of someone who lies during an interrogation can be trusted?” the nobleman asked sharply.

“Guh...” Renji finally felt a sense of danger and shot up out of his seat. The next moment, the knights behind the interrogator parted left and right to surround Renji.

“Don’t act rash, now. It’s my job to reveal the truth. However, if a suspect struggles or attempts to flee, I cannot guarantee you’ll keep your life,” the plump interrogator warned sharply.

“...” Renji glared at the two knights approaching him in succession to keep them in check.

“Seize him.”

At the interrogator’s order, the two knights promptly closed in on Renji. They charged forward with vigor in order to capture Renji, who had backed up all the way to the wall.

Two knights who had undergone military training, versus Renji who had been a normal high school student just days ago. The difference in their physiques was clear as day, and it was only a matter of time before the shorter-than-average Renji was apprehended, no matter how much he struggled.

“Oh no!” Rhea squeezed her eyes shut against the heartbreaking scene. However, the next moment, something happened that no one other than Renji could have predicted.

“Haaah!” Renji, who had been cornered against the wall, suddenly charged towards one of the advancing knights.

“Ugh... Guh...!” The knight approaching from the right received Renji’s tackle and was sent flying towards the wall. He proceeded to crash through the thin wood and tumble outside.

“Wha...” Those who had witnessed that scene were all frozen speechless. In the next moment, Renji used that chance to send the knight approaching from the left flying with all his might as well.

“Nngh?!”

The knight that was sent flying crashed through the wall just like the other knight. The events were so unexpected, the entire room fell silent.

Everyone watched Renji, frozen.

“Hah... Hah...” Renji must have been intensely agitated, as his breathing was heavy while he looked down at his hands with bloodshot eyes.

“R-Renji...?” In a state of shock, Rhea called his name with a trembling voice.

“...” Renji slowly raised his face and stared at the entrance where Rhea was.

“Eek!” Rhea shrank away, clearly terrified.

Renji gulped. “...It’s not my fault. I didn’t do anything wrong!” he yelled while running towards the destroyed wall.

“D-Don’t let him escape! Kill him if you must!” the inspector yelled at the knights outside.

The knights were on high alert after the house’s wall was destroyed and awaiting Renji at the broken wall. They all had their swords drawn.

“Come, Cocytus!”

Renji materialized his divine halberd as soon as he was out of the house. The knights froze in their tracks for a brief moment, before they all recited the spell to enchant their physical ability and slashed their swords at Renji together.

“Augendae Corporis!”

“Raaargh!”

Renji swung his halberd desperately at the knights closing in on him. His movements were completely those of an amateur, but he had overwhelming physical strength. The axehead at the end of the halberd sliced through the bodies of the knights like a knife through paper.

“Wha...”

The interrogator that belatedly appeared from the destroyed wall watched Renji fight, lost for words. Where did he get the halberd from? Why were the experienced knights being slaughtered without even putting up a fight...?

“U-Urgh...”

When Rhea and the villagers saw the scene, they pressed their hands to their mouths to hold back their nausea.

“Y-You monster! Ignis Iecit!”

The interrogator nobleman pointed the wand that was hanging at his waist at Renji and recited a spell that would kill a regular human upon contact. A magic circle immediately appeared at the end of the wand, forming a fireball over a meter large that was fired towards Renji’s back.

“R-Renji!” Rhea screamed right away.

“Wha?!”

Renji promptly turned back and used his momentum to swing his halberd. Then, a sturdy spear of ice shot out of the spike at the tip. The spear of ice pierced through the fireball easily, passing smoothly through the torso of the interrogator behind it.

“Guh...?”

With his wand still raised, the interrogator looked down at the cavity in his abdomen. The next moment, he fell forward with a thud. Everyone could tell he had died instantly. There were still three knights left.

“Aaahhh!”

They all fled as fast as they could, leaving behind the corpses of the interrogator and other knights.

“Hah... Hah... Hah...”

Renji panted heavily, frozen in his stance after swinging his halberd. Silence fell for a long moment.

“S-Shit. What have you done? You’ve killed a noble that was visiting the village. This is b-bad. Very, very bad...” the village chief muttered with a pale face, having accepted the scene before him as reality.

Immediately beside him was Rhea’s childhood friend Yoran, who stepped forward.

“Wh-What have you done?! Are you trying to bring this village to ruin?!”

“Y-Yoran!” Rhea tried to hold Yoran back in a fluster.

“Shut up, Rhea! This all started with you letting that monster stay in this village! Now there’s a dead noble! What are you going to do about it?!” Yoran said, looking around at the corpses on the ground.

“I-I didn’t... That’s...” Rhea turned deathly pale as she struggled for words with tears in her eyes.

“You’re not the one at fault. It’s all that guy’s fault!” The blood seemed to be rushing to Yoran’s head, as he pointed to Renji and yelled hysterically.

“...” Renji glared at Yoran.

“Wh... What, are you going to kill me too?” Yoran squeaked in fear.

“...”

“What about it? Huh? Huh?! Don’t just stay silent, say something!”

Renji’s silence gave Yoran more confidence. Eventually, he was encouraged enough to move closer, grabbing Renji by the shoulder and shaking him. Then, with the exception of Rhea, all the villagers began to look at Renji with angered gazes.

“H-Hey! Stop it, Yoran!” Rhea called for him to stop, but Yoran’s anger only intensified.

“I’m not stopping! It’s all this bastard’s fault!”

“...”

“You—Hey!”

“Don’t touch me!”

“Gah?!”

Enraged at Renji’s continued silence, Yoran finally raised his fist, but Renji punched him back and sent him rolling across the ground. He didn’t use as much strength as when he had sent the knights flying earlier, but Yoran was bleeding from the mouth.

“Huh...?” Yoran looked up at Renji’s face as though to ask why he was punched.

“Don’t try to take this opportunity to look cool. Piece of trash. What I did was legitimate self-defense.”

That’s why I wasn’t at fault. I didn’t do anything bad. Renji looked down at Yoran, emphasizing his point.

“Renji...” Rhea called Renji’s name sadly.

“I...” Renji opened his mouth to say something.

I’m not at fault. That’s why I want you to come with me!

He was driven by the impulse to yell that and reach for Rhea’s hand. However, Renji drew his hand back. Then, he averted his gaze from Rhea with a guilty conscience. “If you guys attack me, I won’t hold back,” he said, glaring back at the village onlookers looking at him with critical gazes.

“Oh...”

The villagers backed away in fear.

“...” Renji bit down on his lip and started running to flee the village. Beyond that was the lake where Renji stood when he first wandered into this world, and farther beyond that was the Vilkis Kingdom’s enemy nation, the Rubia Kingdom.